Richard A. Jenson collection, Inclusive: 1982-1997, undated; Bulk: 1988-1992, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Richard A. Jenson collection
Inclusive: 1982-1997, undated; Bulk: 1988-1992, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
76
Jenson, Richard A.
5 document boxes and 6 oversized boxes.
The Richard A. Jenson collection contains political campaign materials related to all branches of government at the federal, state, and local levels. State, local, and organization-level materials are primarily related to Texas politics from the 1980s and 1990s.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Richard A. Jenson, President of Jenson Research and Communications, founded his Austin-based business in 2005. Jenson had previously served as a consultant for political candidates in Texas, including Texas Supreme Court Justices John Hill, C.L. Ray, Franklin Spears, Ted Robertson, and Bill Kilgarlin.
Jenson extensively collected political campaign materials from the 1980s and 1990s. These include all branches and levels of government, but Jenson's prime areas of interest were the Texas Supreme Court and Appellate Court judicial races. Jenson donated the collection in 2014.
Scope and Content
The Richard A. Jenson collection dates from 1982 to 1997, with the bulk of the records being from 1988 to 1992.
Collection materials are largely related to Texas political campaigns for all levels and branches of government, primarily focusing on the judicial and legislative branches, which comprise the two largest series. Material types include correspondence, fliers, clippings, posters, buttons, VHS tapes, and audio cassettes.
There is a notable geographic focus on campaigns in the Travis County area, including local politics. Political candidates represented in the collection whose materials are housed at Poage Library include Jack Hightower, Chet Edwards, Bob Bullock, and Bill Vance.
Overall, the collection is in good condition.
Arrangement
The Richard A. Jenson collection was originally housed in binders and did not have a discernible order. The collection was removed from its prior housing and an artificial order was imposed. The collection is now arranged into four series: I. Parties and Organizations, II. Executive, III. Judicial, and IV. Legislative. Within each series, folders are organized by level of government: federal, state, and local.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 76. Acquired 2014-07-24
Related Resources
Related references
"Kilgarlin at Weight Center." The Paris News. May 19, 1988. Accessed April 22, 2022.
Richard A. Jenson collection, Accession #76, Control File, Baylor Collections of Political Materials, W. R. Poage Legislative Library, Baylor University.
Index Terms
Subjects (Organizations)
Texas. Supreme Court.
Places
Texas -- Politics and government.; Texas--Politics and government--20th century.; Travis County (Tex.) -- History.
Subjects
Political campaigns -- Texas.; Political candidates -- Texas.; United States -- Politics and government.
Genres
Audiocassettes.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Fliers (Ephemera); Political posters.; VHS.
- Parties and Organizations, 1984-1995, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  Series I. Parties and Organizations do not focus on individual candidates but rather on political parties and organizations. The folders are organized alphabetically by entity with the State Bar of Texas, Texas Democratic Party, and Texas Railroad Commission featuring prominently. Overall, the series is in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Cassette tape; Video home system (VHS) tapes
  - AFL-CIO, Hubbard Cantrell, Campaign Button, undated (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Alliance for Judicial Funding, Inc., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, circa 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Americans for Democratic Action, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Austin City Council, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Austin Progressive Coalition, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Austin Women’s Political Caucus, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Austin/Sheinkopf, VHS Tape, “Trial Lawyer Demo”, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Austin/Sheinkopf, VHS Tape, “1995 Demo Reel” (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - B’nai B’rith, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bexar County Democratic Party, Hall of Fame and Awards Banquet, 1987 July 9 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Campaigns & Elections, Workshop, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Campaign Media, Cassette Tape, “Award Winners”, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Media, VHS Tape, “The Power to Change More Minds”, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Citizens for Austin’s Convention Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Citizens for Qualified Judges, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Committee for a Qualified Judiciary, circa 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dallas Democratic Forum, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dallas Gay Political Caucus, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Democratic National Committee, General, 1988, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Democratic National Committee, Paul Kirk, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Democratic National Convention, From Your House to the White House Party, 1988, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Democratic Party of Hidalgo County, Richard Alamia, Chairman, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee, circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Five Hundred Club, Republican National Committee, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Fleming, Hovenkamp, & Grayson, Judicial Races, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Fund for a Democratic Texas, VHS Tape, “Burning”, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Harris County AFL-CIO, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Harris County Democratic Party, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Henry Sheinkopf Communications Ltd., Cassette Tape, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Hidalgo County Bar Association, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Innovative Resources, Propositions 100 & 106, Window Signs, 1988 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - League of Women Voters, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - McKinnin Media Taral PAC, VHS Tape, “Choice”, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Mexican American Democrats of Texas, Maria Luisa Mercado, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - National Feminist Census, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - National Republican Coalition for Choice, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper Association of America, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Political Accountability Committee, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Potter-Randall Democratic Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - President’s Club, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Progressive Voter’s League, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Republican National Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Republican Presidential Task Force, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Rindy & Associates, VHS Tape, “Demo Reel October 1995”, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Rindy & Associates, VHS Tape, “Democrats”, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Rindy & Associates, VHS Tape, “Fall Election 1988” (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Rindy & Associates, VHS Tape, “1988 Democratic Primary Campaigns” (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Rindy & Associates, VHS Tape, “Worker’s Compensation 3 spots”, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - School Board, Lidia Perex (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - State Bar of Texas, General, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - State Bar of Texas, Joe Cannon, President-Elect Nominee, circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - State Bar of Texas, Oliver Heard, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - State Bar of Texas, Darrell Jordan, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - State Bar of Texas, Lonny Morrison, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - State Bar of Texas, Jim Parsons, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - State Bar of Texas, Robert H. Thomas, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - State Democratic Executive Committee, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Texans for Civil Justice, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Texans for Judicial Integrity, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Texans for the Right to Vote, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Texans for Workplace Insurance Reform, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Texas Abortion Rights Action League, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Texas AFL-CIO Maquiladora Task Force Campaign Button, undated (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Texas AFL-CIO, Harry Hubbard, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Texas Democratic Party, General, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Texas Democratic Party, Cassette Tape, 2 60-second advertisements, “2 Live Bull” and “Crime”, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Texas Democratic Party, Hazel Obey, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Texas Democratic Victory Fund, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Texas Democratic Women, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Texas Energy Reporter, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Texas Medical Association, VHS Tape, “The Fight to Defend the Court”, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Texas Medical Political Action Committee, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Texas Railroad Commission, Lena Guerrero, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Texas Railroad Commission, Clint Hackney, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Texas Railroad Commission, John Henderson, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Texas Railroad Commission, Jim Langdon, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Texas Railroad Commission, Jim Nugent, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Texas Railroad Commission, Barry Williamson, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Texas Victory ’88, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Texas Young Democrats, undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Travis County Democratic Party, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - U.S. Committee for the Battle of Normandy Museum, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - United Farm Workers of America, undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Waller County Democratic Party, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - West Austin Democrats, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Executive, 1986-1997, undated; 2
  Series II. Executive is organized by level of government: federal, state, and local. Within each level, folders are arranged alphabetically by the candidate's last name.
  The federal section is largely related to U.S. presidential races. Prominent historical figures such as George H. W. Bush, Bill Clinton, Al Gore, and Michael Dukakis are represented here.
  In the state section, materials on positions such as governor, lieutenant governor, attorney general, and comptroller can be found. Prominent Texas leaders like Bob Bullock and Chet Edwards are represented here.
  The local section is the largest part of this series and is primarily related to positions in Travis County, Texas. Folders contain materials on mayoral candidates, county commissioners, and sheriffs.
  Overall, this series is in good condition.
  - Federal, Bruce Babbitt, President, circa 1988 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Federal, George H. W. Bush, President, circa 1988 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Federal, George H. W. Bush, President, Window Sign, circa 1988 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Federal, Bill Clinton, President, circa 1994 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Federal, Bob Dole, President, circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Federal, Michael Dukakis, President, 1988, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Federal, Michael Dukakis, President, Campaign Button (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Federal, Michael Dukakis, President, Campaign Button (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Federal, Michael Dukakis, President, Window Sign, circa 1988 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Federal, Dick Gephardt, President, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Federal, Dick Gephardt, President, Campaign Button, circa 1987 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Federal, Al Gore, President, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Federal, Tom Harkin, President, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Federal, Jesse Jackson, President, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Federal, Jesse Jackson, President, Campaign Button, 1988 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Federal, Bob Kerrey, President, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Federal, Lyndon LaRouche, President, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Federal, Walter Mondale, President, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Federal, Pat Robertson, President, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Federal, Paul Simon, President, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - State, Roy Barrera, Jr., Attorney General, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - State, Andrew C. Briscoe III, Governor, circa 1980s (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - State, John Bryant, Attorney General, 1989, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - State, Bob Bullock, Lieutenant Governor, circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - State, Bob Bullock, Lieutenant Governor, Campaign Button, circa 1990s (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - State, Bill P. Clements, Jr., Governor, 1986-1988, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - State, Chet Edwards, Lieutenant Governor, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - State, Armando Gutierrez, Treasurer, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - State, Jim Hightower, Commissioner, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - State, William Hobby, Lieutenant Governor, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - State, Ray Mabus, Governor of Mississippi, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - State, Jim Mattox, Attorney General, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - State, Gary Mauro, Land Commissioner, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - State, Peyton McKnight, Governor, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - State, Dan Morales, Attorney General, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - State, John Odam, Attorney General, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - State, Ann Richards, Governor, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - State, John Sharp, Comptroller, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - State, Royce West, Attorney General, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - State, Mark White, Comptroller, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - State, Clayton Williams, Governor, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Local, Robert Barnstone, Mayor, Austin, circa 1991 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Local, Sam Biscoe, Precinct 1 Commissioner, Austin, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Local, Phil Bredesen, Mayor, Nashville, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Local, Cecilia Burke, Tax Assessor Collector, Travis County, 1988, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Local, Lee Cooke, Mayor, Austin, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Local, Frank Cooksey, Mayor, Austin, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Local, Bruce Elfant, District Clerk, Travis County, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Local, H. N. Ewing, Tax Assessor, Potter County, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Local, Jeff Friedman, Mayor, Austin, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Local, David Langston, Mayor, Lubbock, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Local, Brig Marmolejo, Sheriff, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Local, Rebecca McGee, Tax Assessor, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Local, Charles Miles, County Commissioner, Travis County, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Local, Ron Mullen, Mayor, Austin, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Local, Henry “Fox” Munoz, Jr., Tax Assessor, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Local, Donald Nesby, Constable, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Local, Ken Oden, County Attorney, Travis County, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Local, Ralph Pacheco, County Treasurer, Travis County, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Local, Roger Peterson, Sheriff, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Local, Al Quinto, County Commissioner, Potter County, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Local, Pam Reed, County Commissioner, Travis County, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Local, Alan Sager, County Commissioner, Travis County, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Local, Steve Scott, County Commissioner, Potter County, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Local, Eddie Shell, County Attorney, Travis County, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Local, Jimmy Snell, County Commissioner, Travis County, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Local, Stacy Suits, Constable, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Local, Bruce Todd, Mayor, Austin, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Local, Victor Trevino, Constable, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Judicial, 1982-1994, undated; 3
  Series III. Judicial is organized by level of government: state and local. There are no federal judicial materials present. Within each level of government, folders are organized alphabetically by the candidate's last name.
  The state section accounts for the majority of this series. It relates to candidates for the Texas Supreme Court and Appellate Court judicial races. Jack Hightower, Bill Vance, Jimmy Carroll, Bill Kilgarlin, Oscar Mauzy, Tom Phillips, and Ted Robertson feature prominently.
  The local section consists of materials relating to county court positions as well as Justices of the Peace.
  This series is in good condition.
  Reel to reel tapes; Video home system (VHS) tapes
  - State, Marilyn Aboussie, Third Court of Appeals, 1987, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - State, Kathleen “K.C.” Anderson, 167th District Court, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - State, Charles F. Baird, Texas Court of Criminal Appeals, 1992, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - State, Paul Banner, Texas Supreme Court, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - State, Jim Bates, Texas 13th Court of Appeals, 1988, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - State, John L. Bates, Texas Supreme Court, Campaign Button, 1984 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - State, Karl O. Bayer, Jr., Texas Supreme Court, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - State, Pete Benavides, Texas Court of Criminal Appeals, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - State, Fred Biery, Texas Supreme Court, circa 1990s (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - State, Fred Biery, Texas Supreme Court, Nail File, undated (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - State, Jim Brady, Texas Court of Appeals, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - State, Don Burgess, Texas Supreme Court, 1987, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - State, Robert M. Campbell, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - State, Ron Carr, Texas Court of Appeals, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - State, Ron Carr, Court of Appeals, VHS Tape, “Carr’s Record/Endorse”, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - State, Jimmy Carroll, Texas 3rd Court of Appeals, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - State, Jimmy Carroll, Texas Supreme Court, 1993, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - State, Jimmy Carroll, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Alt 1A, Alt 1B, Alt 1C, Alt 2A, Alt 2B”, 1994 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - State, Jimmy Carroll, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Best Choice”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - State, Jimmy Carroll, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Ethics”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - State, Jimmy Carroll, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Integrity” (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - State, Jimmy Carroll, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Integrity” (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - State, Jimmy Carroll, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Record” (1 of 2), undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - State, Jimmy Carroll, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Record” (2 of 2), undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - State, Ron Chapman, Texas Court of Criminal Appeals, 1988, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - State, Sam Houston Clinton, Texas Court of Criminal Appeals, circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - State, Eugene A. Cook, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - State, Margaret Cooper, Texas District Judge, circa 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - State, John Cornyn, Texas Supreme Court, 1990, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - State, Council of Justices, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - State, John Creuzot, Criminal District Court No. 4, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - State, Barbara Culver, Texas Supreme Court, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - State, Bonner Dorsey, Texas 13th Court of Appeals, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - State, Benjamin Durant, Texas 174th District Court, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - State, George Ellis, Texas 14th Court of Appeals, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - State, Juan Gallardo, 345th District Court, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - State, Bob Gammage, Third Court of Appeals, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - State, Gary Garrison, District Attorney, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - State, Jay Gibson, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - State, Jay Gibson, Texas Supreme Court, Audio Reel, 1986 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - State, Raul Gonzalez, Texas Supreme Court, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - State, Raul Gonzalez, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape (1 of 2), undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - State, Raul Gonzalez, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape (2 of 2), undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - State, Ben Grant, Texas Supreme Court, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - State, Ray Grill, 98th District Court, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - State, Roberto Guerra, Texas 4th Court of Appeals, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - State, Gary Hall, 68th District Court, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - State, Nathan Hecht, Texas Supreme Court, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - State, Jack Hightower, Texas Supreme Court, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - State, Danny Hill, District Attorney, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - State, Gilberto Hinojosa, 13th Court of Appeals, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - State, Scrappy Holmes, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - State, John Humphreys, Court of Criminal Appeals, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - State, Woodie Jones, Court of Appeals, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - State, Jeff Kaplan, Court of Appeals, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - State, Colin Kaufman, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - State, Jim Keahey, 3rd Court of Appeals, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - State, Joe Kegans, 230th District Court, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - State, Bill Kilgarlin, Texas Supreme Court, 1986-1987, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - State, Bill Kilgarlin, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Bill Kilgarlin”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - State, Bill Kilgarlin, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Judge Kilgarlin”, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - State, Bill Kilgarlin, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “One of the Best” (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - State, Bill Kilgarlin, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “One of the Best” (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - State, Bill Kilgarlin, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “The Choice”, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - State, Bill Kilgarlin, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “The Choice (Revised), 1988 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - State, Jack King, 136th District Court, Nail File, undated (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - State, Frank Lamson, 136th District Court, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - State, Oscar Mauzy, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - State, Oscar Mauzy, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, 1992 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - State, Oscar Mauzy, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Broken Promise”, 1991 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - State, Oscar Mauzy, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Cover Story, The Big Lie, Policeman”, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - State, Oscar Mauzy, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Mauzy vs. Enoch”, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - State, Oscar Mauzy, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Under Investigation”, 1992 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - State, Oscar Mauzy, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Under Investigation”, 1992 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - State, Scott McCown, 345th District Judge, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - State, Jeanne Meurer, 98th District Court, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - State, Margaret Mirabel, 1st Court of Appeals, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - State, Paul Murphy, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - State, Morris Overstreet, Texas Court of Criminal Appeals, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - State, Tom Phillips, Texas Supreme Court, General, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 50)